{
    "id": "15dc3d29a8134a8fb2a26599b49e641d",
    "title": "So, Very, and Too | Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "It was ………………. dark that I could not see anything.",
            "description": "'So' shows the effect or result. ",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "very",
                "too"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "03f71d6addf6412f96db82bdf1752896"
        },
        {
            "question": "The tea is ………………… hot for me to drink.",
            "description": "Note the pattern 'too...to'.",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "so",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "aaf7de2218fc46c28451336b1ec88208"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was …………………. busy to meet them.",
            "description": "Note the pattern 'too...to'. We use 'too' to indicate undesirable extremes. ",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "too",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b7e1b01185fc4e80bb7e74b607770859"
        },
        {
            "question": "The evening was ………………. cold.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "very",
                "too",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "01e79b534fcd4553953da6d8a0c8944c"
        },
        {
            "question": "There are far ……………….. many mistakes in the essay.",
            "description": "Far can modify 'too many', but it cannot modify 'very many'.",
            "answers": [
                "very",
                "too",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e6d52b52482c4c44bf9efe120b833665"
        },
        {
            "question": "He behaved ……………….. rudely that we wanted to slap him.",
            "description": "Note the pattern 'so...that'.",
            "answers": [
                "very",
                "so",
                "too"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1bf2baff2e8041b7aaea4986e4aca594"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am ……………….. happy today.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "very",
                "too",
                "Either so or very"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "c2fad84d100c486c9e4728faa33637dc"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………….. many people agree with me.",
            "description": "In some situations both 'so' and very' are possible with similar meanings. ",
            "answers": [
                "So",
                "Very",
                "Too",
                "Either so or very"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "a1cf2b737bbb46f0a9b62ffc13c55533"
        },
        {
            "question": "The coat was ……………….. expensive that I didn’t buy it.",
            "description": "Note the pattern 'so...that'.",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "so",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "343849127b5646688502201e0cc2c06a"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is .................................... frail to walk without support.",
            "description": "Note the pattern 'too...to'.",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "too",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "56968339701b445fa561dc10e79ba996"
        }
    ]
}